http://www.purdueexponent.org/site/privacy.html

West Lafayette, IN
(47906)
Today
Partly cloudy skies during the morning hours will become overcast in the afternoon. High 58F. Winds S at 5 to 10 mph..
Tonight
Rain. Low 51F. Winds SSE at 10 to 15 mph. Chance of rain 100%. Rainfall near a half an inch.
Contact Us
8:30 a.m. to 5 p.m.
Site
Privacy PolicyEffective date Sept. 15, 2017; Updated March 27, 2018 Overview     The Purdue Student Publishing Foundation owns and operates a Web site known asThe Purdue Exponent online ("our site"). The privacy practices of this statementapply to our services available and operated under the domain(s) and/orsubdomain(s) of www.purdueexponent.org , www.purdueexponent.com andwww.exponenthousing.com. By visiting our site you agree to be bound by the termsand conditions of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, do not use or access oursite. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of information our site gathers aboutvisitors and the ways in which we use and don't use that information.      By accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy through accessing the servicesprovided, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personalinformation in accordance with this Privacy Policy.      We reserve the right to amend or modify our Privacy Policy at any time in thefuture, in which case we will post a revised Privacy Policy on our site and update theEffective Date to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use our site afterwe post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified. Therefore, youshould check periodically for an updated policy. All amended terms areautomatically effective once they are posted on our site.     We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website. These companies may use information (not including any Personally-Identifying Information) about your visits to the Website and other websites that are contained in Web Cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Using a tool created by the Network Advertising Initiative, you can opt out of several third-party ad servers' and networks' Web Cookies simultaneously. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please complete the following links:   http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp,   http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/, or http://www.aboutads.info/choices/. Please contact us if you would like to know the identity of the third-party advertising companies we are currently using to serve ads.      We may allow advertisers to choose the characteristics of users who will see their advertisements, and we may use any of the Non-Personally Identifying Information we have collected (including information you may have decided not to show to other users, such as your birth year or other sensitive personal information or preferences) to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements. We do not identify you to the advertiser. https://privacy.thewaltdisneycompany.com/en/privacy-controls/online-tracking-and-advertising/     Advertisers and third parties also may collect information about your activity on our sites and applications, on devices associated with you, and on third-party sites and applications using tracking technologies. Tracking data collected by these advertisers and third parties is used to decide which ads you see both on our sites and applications and on third-party sites and applications, but does not identify you personally and is not associated with your registration account. You may choose not to receive targeted advertising from many ad networks, data exchanges, marketing analytics and other service providers. You may also choose to control targeted advertising you receive within applications by using your mobile device settings (for example, by re-setting your device's advertising identifier and/or opting out of interest based ads). We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. https://www.washingtonpost.com/privacy-policy/2011/11/18/gIQASIiaiN_story.html?utm_term=.a3b1c281187e     As described above, we and third parties may use cookies and other tracking technologies to facilitate serving relevant ads to you. For example, these technologies help us determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before, tailor ads to you if you have visited our site before, and avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. You can learn more about certain types of targeted advertising by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance website or our Ad Choices page.     In addition to disabling cookies and other tracking technologies as described above, you may opt-out of receiving targeted advertising from participating ad networks, audience segment providers, ad serving vendors, and other service providers by visiting websites operated by the Network Advertising Initiative and Digital Advertising Alliance . http://syvnews.com/privacy/About Third Party Advertising      We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you use our Services. If so, a list of these ad serving companies will be available here. These companies may use information (generally, not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to our sites or use of our Services and to other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses' privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer website.      Google Doubleclick for Publishers (DFP) is an ad network partner that displays ads on our Services. To improve your ad experience on our sites and Services and elsewhere on the Internet, we may send non-personal information to Google DFP based on your browser's activities, such as type of pages viewed and categories of interests, so that the advertising you see is relevant to you. Google DFP also may use information regarding its own users to select which ads to display. Click here to learn more about Google DFP's ad practices, including how to opt out of using anonymous information to select which ads to show you. Opt-Out of Cookies     If you wish to manage or opt-out of cookies utilized by our site and third party advertisers, you can take the following steps:You may be able to download an opt-out cookie from the third party advertiser's website allowing you to opt-out of cookies. Please visit the third party advertiser's websites for more information.Your web browser may allow you to manage what cookies are accepted or declined. These settings can usually be found in the preferences or options menus of your web browser.Your web browser may also allow you to manually view cookies and delete the cookies you don't want or need. Check your web browser's settings for more information.Websites that require registration may allow you to opt-out of cookies. Check the account settings or preferences section of the website for more information.For more information, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.       This Privacy Policy applies to The Purdue Exponent online and any subdomainsdescribed above and does not cover any other activities or services, including printpublishing, undertaken by The Purdue Exponent.Information that is automatically gatheredDuring normal Web browsing, our site automatically logs information based on yourbehavior on the site, which may include:(1.) The URL that you just came from and to which URL you go next.(2.) Your Internet Protocol (IP) address.(3.) The date, time and length of time of your visit.(4.) Any page you visited.(5.) Your computer operating system and browser type and version (if provided bythe browser).(6.) Search words you use to search our site.      The information collected does not identify you by name or any other personallyidentifiable fact. The information is used in aggregate form for internal reportingand marketing purposes. For example, we publicly release how many visitors oursite receives on a monthly basis.      The Purdue Exponent reserves the right to use client- or server-based cookies or"Web beacons" to track activity on our site and enhance traffic statisticalinformation. However, companies that display ads or provide services on our sitemay use cookies or other tracking mechanisms. Their use of these technologies isgoverned by their privacy policies. "Cookies" are small files placed on your harddrive that assist the service provider in developing and providing its services.      The Purdue Exponent occasionally offers services provided by external third partiesto provide linked services for visitors of Web sites operated by The PurdueExponent. The privacy policy of the external third party applies, not our PrivacyPolicy. If you visit one of these linked sites or a Collegian Web page that uses anexternal organization's services, you should first review that organization's privacypolicy and its other policies.      The Purdue Exponent is not responsible in any way for the content or policies ofother organizations, and cannot protect information you provide directly to a linkedsite or service.      The Purdue Exponent cannot protect you from unlawful interception by thirdparties.      The Purdue Exponent reserves the right to and may add, change and/or deleteadditional third-party providers for The Purdue Exponent from time to time at anytime without notice. Information provided by users     The Purdue Exponent does not require any type of registration for normal browsing.However, we do sometimes request personal information for specific purposes, suchas verifying a letter to the editor or posting a comment alongside our content.      When we do collect personal information, The Purdue Exponent will use it only forthe purpose for which we requested it. We do not sell or distribute personallyidentifiable information to third parties except where required by law. The PurdueExponent will cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, investigations, andrequests and disclose any information, with or without a subpoena, that is needed tosatisfy any law, regulation or legal request or assist in any investigation of a lawenforcement agency.      Our site is not directed to children younger than the age of 13 years, and we do notknowingly collect or distribute information from or about children younger than theage of 13 years. Your California privacy rights     The California Civil Code gives California residents the right to request fromcompanies conducting business in California a list of all third parties to which thecompany disclosed personal information during the preceding year for directmarketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that if a company has a privacypolicy that gives either an opt-out or opt-in choice for use of your personalinformation by third parties for marketing purposes, the company may insteadprovide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure options.      The Purdue Exponent does not disclose personal information to third parties fordirect marketing purposes. Thus, we are not required to maintain or disclose a listof the third parties that received your personal information for marketing purposesduring the preceding calendar year.– Adapted, by permission, from The Daily Collegian Online.
Facebook
Twitter
YouTube
Instagram
Submit a Letter to the Editor
If you're interested in submitting a Letter to the Editor, click here.
Submit
Upcoming Events
Dec
17
Pan American Aviation Day
Thu, Dec 17, 2020
Articles
Images
Videos
Commented
ArticlesWilliamsport man arrested on allegations of attempted rape, kidnapping from LafayetteRaising Cane's Chicken Fingers to open State Street restaurantWoman charged in stabbing near Wabash LandingDaniels' performance metrics for 2020-2021, professor ratifications approvedFinance site lists West Lafayette as a top college townUniversity Senate reports deepening burnout as semester closesAmanda Bynes is in a 'much healthier place'Purdue Football: Bucket game canceledIn lawsuit, professor who alleged corruption claims he was ‘exiled’Nebraska defeats Purdue, 37-27
Images
Videos
CommentedSorry, there are no recent results for popular commented articles.
Other Headlines
Former Purdue coach Akers dies at 82
Raising Cane's Chicken Fingers to open State Street restaurant
Philly area basketball player commits to Class of 2022
Woman charged in stabbing near Wabash Landing
Williamsport man arrested on allegations of attempted rape, kidnapping from Lafayette
© Copyright 2020 Purdue Exponent, PO Box 2506 West Lafayette, IN | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
